Finding Aid for the Incoming Correspondence: Heinrich Meyer Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Incoming Correspondence: Heinrich Meyer Papers
undated
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0290
20 linear feet
- Aaron, Harold, 28 June 1960
- Abels, Henry. (2), 3 November 1942, 20 November 1942
- Abt, Roslyn. (4), 10 October 1973- 7 November 1973
- Ackerknecht, Erwin. (12), 15 April 1951-5 May 1956
- Ackerman, J. H, 20 August 1946
- Ackermann, Theodor. (5), 10 January 1968-17 January 1973
- Acton, Evelyn B, 28 February 1973
- Adams, George, 28 September 1941
- Adams, I. C., Jr, 25 April 1947
- Adams, J.A, 2 November 1946
- Adams, Taylor, 29 January 1962
- Aden, John M. (2), 17 May 1973 –17 September 1973
- Adler, Arthur M, 29 April 1950
- Adler, Paul, 9 March 1961
- Adolf, Helen (67), 1 May 1965-30 May 1974
- Aesch, A. Gode-von, 9 January 1949
- Aeschlimann, Rudolf. (2), 14 March 1946 –26 December 1946
- Agnew, Janet (28), 30 August 1933 –13 April 1951, undated
- Ahern, Ellen C. (2), 18 February 1947-19 July 1949
- Ahles, Fred M, 24 August 1967
- Albert, Eberhard. (4), 26 October 1953 –30 June 1963
- Albrecht, Erich A, 8 January 1948
- Albrecht, Russo, 26 October 1938, undated
- Albrecht, William A, 23 April 1947
- Aldridge, A. Owen. (4), 17 January 1952-8 July 1974
- Alexis, Joseph, 5 December 1949
- Alker, Ernst. (8), 14 February 1954-16 July 1967
- Alker, Maria, n.d.- 24 October 1972
- Alksin, Ivan. (20), 1 November 1961- 11 April 1967
- Allen, Anna D. (2), 30 January 1952 -13 February 1952
- Allen, Peggy and George. (8), 23 October 1952 –22 November 1955, undated
- Allen, George & Unwin Ltd, 12 September 1946
- Allen, James B, 10 February 1943
- Allen, Jane, 6 September 1951
- Allen, Richard J. (6), 1 November 1973, undated
- Allen, William H. (42), 4 March 1942- 5 August 1970
- Allen, Virginia R. (3), 30 November 1938- 25 October 1939
- Aloe, Edward. (2), 8 December 1948- 26 April 1949
- Alps, Glen. (8), 18 February 1953 -20 December 1961
- d` Alquen Richard. (4), 7 February 1970 –16 March 1970, undated
- Altenburg, Edgar. Undated
- d `Amat, Jean-Marie, 9 February 1953
- Amato, Mario. (25), 1 October 1952-18 October 1955
- Ames, C. T., Jr, 12 May 1948
- Ammon, Bertha A, 5 September 1959
- Anders, Carl, 26 May 1931
- Anders, W. (14), 17 January 1954, undated
- Anderson, J. M, 17 April 1944
- Andrews, Paul R. (2), 20 September 1944 –2 October 1944
- Angell, Richard, 3 October 1951
- Angelloz, J. F. (5), 31 July 1952-20 December 1955
- Angelucci, Antoinette. (2), 6 April 1948- 27 April 1948
- Anundsen, Harriet, 3 January 1947
- Anvil, Ken and Mary (7), 11 December 1956, undated
- Appelt, E. P. (7), 27 January 1941-4 December 1949
- Apt, Franz. (2), 20 November 1952-18 January 1953
- Arber, Agnes. (5), 21 April 1947-11 January 1952
- Arber, Muriel. (2), 15 February 1952 –1 March 1952
- Arlt, Gustave O. (3), 23 February 1948- 6 October 1948
- Armour, Grace. Undated
- Armstrong, Eunice B, 7 March 1961
- Arndt, Karl. (27), 3 February 1941- 24 July 1972, undated
- Arnold, Hans-Ulrich. (2), 7 November 1946-2 June 1953
- Aron, Albert. (2), 9 January 1941- 9 September 1943
- Arrè, Aurelia. (4), 11 December 1959-25 December 1962
- Asher, John. (3), 23 October 1970 -22 September 1972
- Asmyte, Ieva, 12 December 1959
- Atkins, Stuart. (30), 21 September 1948- 11 April 1973
- Atkinson, Brooks, 13 March 1964
- Aubjn, ? (18), 19 August 1961- 24 October 1973
- Austin, Margaret, 17 May 1968
- B
  - Baer, E. (3), 14 January 1955- 25 February 1955
  - Baertschi, Hans, 23 August 1966
  - Bagrow, Natalie. (4), 30 March 1948- 27 April 1948
  - Bahanan, Sallye. Undated
  - Bahn, Ehrhared, 30 November 1972
  - Baier, Georg. (3), 10 April 1957- 20 February 1961
  - Baker, Shirley Kistler, 14 December 1971
  - Bailey, L.H, 10 July 1946
  - Baillon, ?, 9 December 1967
  - de Baillou, Clemens, 14 April 1969
  - Baldeschwieler, Agnes Ross [Mrs. Herman]. Undated
  - Baldridge, James Whittington, 25 October 1949
  - Balmer, George. (4), 19 June 1951- 9 January 1953
  - Baltensweiler, Max R, 23 April 1954
  - Balty, Israel, 1 June 1951
  - Bambe, Joe. Undated
  - Bamberger, Lucie (7), 18 October 1960 –14 December 1971
  - Bamberger, Walter (5), 27 January 1954- 22 March 1956
  - Bandy, W.T. (2), 15 December 1971- 7 January 1974
  - Bänziger, Hans, 15 April 1966
  - Barba, Preston and Eleanor. (3), 15 May 1947- 9 July 1950
  - Bard, Guy K, 3 November 1952
  - de Bard, Marianne, 10 August 1953
  - Barlow, Robert O. (5), 5 October 1944- 3 March 1961
  - Barnes & Noble Inc. (6), 9 April 1942 -3 September 1942
  - Barnstorff, Hermann (3), 21 November 1949- 9 December 1958
  - Barrick, Mac E, 2 June 1960
  - Barrouk, Vesta, 7 December 1970
  - Bartel, Klaus. (8), 12 June 1972- 7 July 1973, undated
  - Bartlett, A.C, 14 April 1938
  - Barton, William H, 29 July 1946
  - Basilius, Harold A. (3), 31 March 1950- 4 April 1969
  - Bastian, H.J. (3), 6 July 1950- 16 December 1960
  - Barnston, Henry. (3), 3 May 1938- 5 December 1938
  - Battista, J.L. (6), 22 June 1945- 24 October 1947
  - Bauer, Edward, 11 October 1965
  - Bauer, J, 27 January 1967
  - Bauer, John J. (2), 6 May 1951- 9 September 1951
  - Bauer, ?, 22 June 1949
  - Bauke, Joseph. (9), 6 December 1967- 11 November 1971
  - Baumann, Hans J, 21 January 1954
  - Baumwoll, Dorothy. (2), 6 January 1961- 17 January 1961
  - Baxter, Norman W, 1 July 1941
  - Bayerschmidt, Carl F. (13), 15 June 1948- 21 June 1960
  - Becker, ?, 6 June 1956
  - Benrath, Henry. Undated
  - Berend, Eduard. (7), 18 June 1942- 23 September 1973
  - Bergstraesser, Arnold. (33), 5 January 1946- 26 September 1950
  - Bernard, Jules E. (56), 31 January 1940 –10 June 1953
  - Bernard, R.K. (2), 11 August 1953-21 August 1953
  - Bernreuther, Eberhard. (2), 2 April 1947 -7 July 1947
  - Berrigan, J. Undated
  - Berry, Hertha. (2), 15 May 1969, undated
  - Ber?, 24 November 1944
  - Berthrong, Merrill G, 11 December 1963
  - Best, Tom. (5), 5 October 1962- 2 April 1963
  - Beurning(?), G, 19 April 1951
  - Beutler, Ernst. (2), May 1960- 8 November 1960
  - Bez(?), R, 3 July 1962
  - Bezanson, Stanley O. (21), 19 November 1947 -16 September 1968
  - Bieber, Konrad F, 1 February 1962
  - Biebler, Johann Reinhard (9), 12 January 1950-5 November 1951
  - Biggs, E. Power, 15 October 1973
  - Billeber, Paul, 21 August 1973
  - Birch, Jr., Thomas Harrison. Undated
  - Bircher, Martin, 9 March 1974
  - Bischopfli, January 1956
  - Blackall, Eric (6), 16 December 1960-28 November 1972
  - Blackwell, B.H. Ltd. (53), 16 December 1940-10 July 1973
  - Blair, Naomi B, 5 November 1948
  - Blankenagel, John C. (3), 18 November 1949-23 December 1958
  - Blau, Ludwig W. (39), 2 February 1945-13 December 1963, undated
  - Bloch, Ingram. Undated
  - Bluhm, Heinz. (9), 20 April 1951-29 April 1960
  - Blume, Bernhard (41), 19 May 1944-31 December 1972, undated
  - Blumenberg, Hans. (2), 6 June 1972-27 April 1973
  - Bluth, Otto. (2), 30 December 1973, undated
  - Boardman, Myron L. (2), 2 January 1946 -13 March 1946
  - Bobb, James T, 28 May 1952
  - Bock, O. (2), 10 August 1964, undated
  - Bodger, John. (5), 20 March 1946-14 October 1946
  - Boehm, John and Maria. (5), December 1971-n.d.
  - Boel(?), Jr., John, 8 April 1971
  - Boerner, Peter. (2), 15 January 1973-4 February 1973
  - Boesche, A. W. Undated
  - Böhm,. (2), 9 June 1958-9 July 1958
  - Bolitts(?), Bill, 6 December 1966
  - Boll, Johannes, Willi, and Fritz. Undated
  - Bolzmann, H, 9 December 1943
  - Bondy, Olea, 12 October
  - Bonner, C.M, 28 October 1948
  - Borland, V.L. (2), October 8 1936-November 15 1936
  - Bosch, Paul F. (2), 4 October 1954-5 October 1954
  - Böschenstein, H. (13), 23 April 1952-2 January 1964
  - Bost, Ira H, 19 August 1947
  - Boswell, Jr., Peyton, 8 February 1946
  - Boswell, Victor R, 1 December 1944
  - Bothmer, Gerry, 8 December 1953
  - Bottens, L.E, 18 December 1947
  - van Bourgondien, P.C, 23 July 1947
  - Boult, Reber, 18 June 1968
  - Bourdel, Maurice, 30 September 1955
  - Bovatia, W.W, 15 February 1949
  - Bowcock, James M, 17 July 1936
  - Bowman, Derek (24), 29 June 1961-13 March 1974
  - Boyette, Purvis E, 3 August 1966
  - Brachin, P, 2 August 1952
  - von Bradish, Joesph A, 29 November 1949
  - Bradley, Alida, May. (13) October 1944, undated
  - Bradley, Lyman, 7 October 1940
  - Bradley, Sculley, 22 November 1960
  - Brady, Carol. (3), 24 January 1940, undated
  - Brady, Jo, 25 February 1943
  - Bragg, Marvin, 11 March 1972
  - Brammer, Ursula G. (3), September 1973 -27 January 1974
  - Brand, Joseph, 10 November 1966
  - Brandes, George H. (5), 4 December 1949 –29 December 1951, undated
  - Brandes, H, 15 June 1967
  - Brandes, Marie. Undated
  - Brandt, Joseph A. (2), 22 April 1946-17 May 1946
  - Braun, Frank X, 4 January 1955
  - Braun, W, 28 May 1953
  - von Braun, Frhr, 8 October 1960
  - Bräutigam, ?, 19 October 1971
  - Bray, Gertrude and Hubert. (14) Christmas cards, undated
  - Bredow H.V, 24 February 1946
  - Breehme, Karl F, 26 February 1943
  - Breitling, Evelyn C. Tapham. Christmas card, undated
  - Breland, Osmond P, 14 July 1946
  - Breslauer, Martin. (4), 13 May 1946-16 April 1953
  - Brewer, Edward V, 15 May 1952
  - Brie, F.?, 9 July 1938
  - Briggs, May Bradley. (5) Undated. Also see Alida May Bradley
  - Bristol, Donna, 6 February 1942
  - Britt, Helen J. (2), 22 October 1963-1 November 1963
  - Brockhaus, F.A, 25 September 1960
  - Bromfield, Louis. (2), 26 September 1946- 3 October 1947
  - Bromfield, Ute, 18 July 1961
  - Brookes, John B, 21 January 1954
  - Brooks, Paul (2), 30 January 1948-14 April 1948
  - Brown, Bernice, 8 July 1947
  - Brown, J.N, 18 September 1944
  - Brown, Joseph C, 8 May 1944
  - Brown, Karl, 13 March 1953
  - Brown, Rutte. Undated
  - Brownback, Sally. (3), 19 September 1944-2 October 1944
  - Browning, Robert. (4), 25 January 1955-25 February 1967
  - Bruderhausen, A. (27), 10 August 1940-30 November 1945, undated
  - de Bruine, N.A.C. Slotemaker, 1 February 1950
  - Bruns, Friedrich. (49), 2 November 1943-1 December 1958
  - Bryan, Miriam M. Undated
  - Bub, Douglas F. (2), 1 December 1969 –23 November 1971
  - Buchanan, Emerson, 11 November 1952
  - Buck, George C, 1 March 1956
  - Buck, Pearl S, 23 April 1962
  - Buckman, Thomas R, 20 July 1963
  - Bugbane, Egmont. (3), 10 June 1946, undated
  - Bullhof, Francis, December 1969
  - Bullicfield, Victor L, 14 December 1951
  - Bunker, M. N. Undated
  - Burckhard, Arthur. (67), 16 January 1942 –7 January 1967, undated
  - Burckhard, Dorothea Moore. (3), 31 March 1973 –11 January 1974
  - Burckhard, ? L, 17 May 1932
  - Burckhard, Marie. (2), 1 March 1912 –9 September 1934
  - Burckhard, Oscar, 10 October 1950
  - Burckhardt, Carl. (2), 28 April 1951 –5 December 1963
  - Burckhardt, Lukas F. (4), 10 January 1966 –9 January 1970
  - Burniaux, Constant., 1973
  - Burpee, W. Atlee Company. (2), 21 January 1946 –7 September 1971
  - Burzle, J. A. (4), 28 December 1962 –21 December 1966
  - Busch, Norbert A, 17 May 1965
  - Bush, Elsie, 19 September 1944
  - Bush, ?, 25 March 1952
  - Buss, Siegfried A, 30 November 1972
  - Bussie, George, 21 June 1973
  - Butler, Beth S, 7 February 1946
  - Butler, Ernst, 5 July 1952
  - Byers, Calvin and Lois. (7), 19 March 1946 –20 March 1947
  - Byrd, Cecil K. (2), 9 October 1962 –10 June 1963
- C
  - Caldwell, Robert, 14 March
  - Calogero, Guido, 20 September 1967
  - Camden, Carroll. (3), 26 February 1953 –7 June 1953
  - Cameron, R. C, 12 March 1956
  - Campbell, Robertina, 19 November 1952
  - Campbell, Ruth. (2), 14 October 1944 –25 October 1944
  - von Campe, Siegfried, 2 June 1959
  - Cantieni, Margaret and Joe. (6), 18 December 1951-1963, undated
  - Carini, Mary L, 6 March 1952
  - Carman, Harry J, 10 March 1949
  - Carpenter, Edward, 17 December 1944
  - Carrier, Carl. (16), 31 July 1951 –22 July 1970, undated
  - Carroll, Mary. Undated
  - Carter, Sims. (3), 16 December 1948 –25 January 1949
  - Casalini, Mario, 7 March 1968
  - Casson, Nedda, 9 September 1946
  - Cerf, Bennett A. (2), 14 May 1947 –9 January 1950
  - Champie, Ellmore A, 5 January 1952
  - Chance, Burton, 14 October 1933
  - Chandler, Asa C. Undated
  - Chapman, H. D, 14 July 1945
  - Charlesworth, Bill. (7), 1 January 1954 –23 September 1957
  - Chatham, Gina, 3 September 1973
  - Childs, J. Rives. (3), 13 May 1963 –19 December 1971
  - Chilson, Francis, 30 October
  - Cioffari, Vincenzo. (2), 30 November 1949 –8 December 1949
  - Cioffi, Bette and Anthony. Christmas card, undated [see also Bette Treichler]
  - Claassen, 31 May 1952
  - Clampitt, Amy, 18 November 1947
  - Clanton, Glen F, 1 March 1971
  - Clark, A. N, 12 January 1945
  - Clark, Audrey and Norman. (83), 25 August 1948 –8 October 1971, undated
  - Clark, Bennett Champ, 15 November 1939
  - Clark, Bert, 19 February 1949
  - Clark, George A. and Georgina. (127), 6 April 1943 –1 August 1968, undated
  - Clark, Robert T. (11), 11 February 1941 –17 January 1955, undated
  - Clark, ? [Mother of Doris] (23), 9 December 1952 –27 October 1955, undated
  - Clattenberg, Albert E, 3 December 1942
  - Clements, E. S, 17 August 1945
  - Clifford, John C. (9), 17 March 1946 –5 April 1947
  - Clifford, Simone. Undated
  - Coddington, Parker L. (2), 23 May 1967 –6 May 1970
  - Cogley, John, 9 December 1971
  - Cohen, I. Bernard. (2), 2 July 1952 –22 April 1958
  - Cohen, Matthew, 8 March 1956
  - Cohn, Hilde D. (4), 25 May 1953 –12 September 1972
  - Cohn, J. J. (3), 17 February 1947 –22 April 1947
  - Cole, C. N, 9 April 1935
  - Cole, Lois Dwight. (2), 9 October 1944 –16 October 1944
  - Cole, Tom. (2), 22 August 1950 –1952
  - Coleman, Lester L, 1 February 1962
  - Collins, Ethel D. W. (3), 11 July 1947, undated
  - Collinson, Priscilla, 1 December 1954
  - Collis, W. P, 24 November 1944
  - Conley, John J, 18 November 1965
  - Connally, Tom. (5), 8 July 1939 –25 November 1941
  - Conner, Alice, 29 January 1973
  - Cooper, E. W, 2 August 1948
  - Cooper, Renee E, 21 November 1952
  - Cooperrider, Edward E. (3), 10 December 1962 –14 January 1963
  - Copeland, Edith. (20), 9 October 1964 –21 April 1967
  - Corbett, J. P, 17 October 1972
  - Graf Coudenhove-Calergi, 16 April 1961
  - Cousins, Norman. (3), 2 February 1972, undated
  - Covington, Judith, 23 September 1954
  - Cowan, J. M, 17 December 1963
  - Cowen, Richard, 15 July 1952
  - Cowles, Alfred, 13 May 1941
  - Cowles, Porter, 23 November 1945
  - Crafts, A. J. (3), 13 December 1944 –26 December 1944
  - Crawford, John, 23 January 1974
  - Cress, Allan M, 21 January 1953
  - Creswick, H. R, 9 November 1966
  - Criswell, Lloyd. Undated
  - Cullinan, J, 31 July
  - Cummings, P. M. (2), 9 August, undated
  - Cunningham, Dale S. (2), 8 February 1960 –14 February 1960
  - Cunningham, Geo. G, 13 November 1941
  - Cunningham, S. B, 3 March 1945
  - Cunz, Dieter (3), 15 June 1967 –1968
  - Currie, W. H, 10 May 1947
  - Curt, Kurser, 27 March 1953
  - Curschmann, Michael. (2), 15 September 1970 -17 June 1972
  - Cushing, Frederic S, 1 March 1955
  - Cuthbertson, Stuart. (5), 26 July 1949 –11 April 1950
- D
  - Dahl, Harry K, 2 May 1945
  - Dallett, Joseph B. (3), 8 June 1972 –5 July 1972
  - Danton, Emily M. (3), 13 July 1943 –15 October 1943
  - Danton, George H. (18), 4 January 1934 –23 July 1947, undated
  - Danzer, Anton, 15 June 1950
  - Darlington, C. D, 7 June 1946
  - Dasypodius, N. Undated
  - Davidson, Angus, 20 October 1929
  - Daub, Albert. (2), 14 January 1948 –8 December 1954
  - Davidson, Donald, 25 February 1964
  - Davidson, Dorothy F, 8 August 1970
  - Davidson, Helen, 3 March
  - Davidson, John S. (2), 19 August 1949 -25 June 1952
  - Davidson, Margie. (2), 7 May 1967 –17 June 1967
  - Davis, Alice B. (2), 12 September 1949 –8 December 1952
  - Davis, Elmer, 12 July 1940
  - Davis, R. O. E. (2), 12 December 1946 –20 December 1946
  - Deahl, Carolyn. Christmas card, 1952
  - Deblev, ? (11), 10 November 1952 –21 April 1955, undated
  - Deevey, Ed. (11), 25 October 1943 –13 July 1953
  - Degeur, Otto. (7), 24 December 1944 –20 March 1946
  - Dekker, Piet, 6 May 1950
  - Delany, Frank J, 10 October 1950
  - Delattre, Pierre, 12 May 1948
  - Delzell, Charles F, 7 March 1972
  - Demelius, Christa. (2), 9 July 1968 –10 December 1969
  - Demetz, Hana and Peter. (2), 1957 –15 June 1965
  - Denkler, Horst. (6), 22 November 1971 –28 November 1972, undated
  - Denny, Maggie. (4), 16 August 1957, undated
  - Derks, Paul, 25 March 1970
  - Detwiler, S. B. (2), 30 January 1946 –21 November 1946
  - Deuticke, Franz. (12), 9 September 1949 –24 October 1962, undated
  - Deutsch, Alma. (4), 18 November 1954 –16 April 1973
  - Deutsch, Morton, 26 September 1960
  - Devitt, Andy B. (2), 4 September 1945 –17 July 1947
  - deV?, R.W. Undated
  - DeVolld, Walter L, 11 November 1965
  - Dies, Martin, 17 July 1940
  - Dietz, Mary Ann and Guenther. (2) Christmas cards, undated
  - Dihoff, Ivan. Undated
  - Dilley, Elizabeth. Undated
  - Dimler, G. Richard. (9), 26 July 1972, undated
  - Dinkelacker, Horst, 25 August 1971
  - Dinsmoor, Carlton G. (3), 9 April 1939 –7 October 1939
  - Dippleberger, Augustus, 24 May 1945
  - Dippleberger, Fairfax. Undated
  - Dix, William S. (3), 4 January 1952 –21 December 1971
  - Dolson, L. L, 6 May 1947
  - Donlen, M. A. (2), 12 May 1942 –16 May 1942
  - Donnelly, R. A, 30 November 1954
  - Dorling, F, 22 January 1962
  - Dorn, Knut, 1 December 1967
  - Dorn, Richard W, 9 July 1968
  - Dornback, Schwabinger (2), December 1957 –30 December 1959
  - Dorrance, Anne, 21 May 1947
  - Doubleday, Doran and Company. (3), 14 December 1944 –14 February 1945
  - Dougherty, David M, 17 December 1948
  - Dougherty, Nan. Christmas card, undated
  - Douglas, David, 18 January 1952
  - Downs, R. B. (3), 22 September 1952 –13 October 1952
  - Doyle, W. V, 26 January 1953
  - Drell, T, 4 November 1944
  - Drewitz, Ingeborg, 30 January 1971
  - Drimler, G. R, 11 July 1972
  - Drury, Allen, 2 September 1959
  - Du, Ed and Georgie. Christmas card, undated
  - Du Faur, Curt von Faber, 4 June
  - Duff, James H, 6 June 1951
  - Duisurvor, Nelle L, 1 April 1936
  - Duncan, Bernice G. (6), 26 February 1952 –14 December 1966
  - Duncan, Elizabeth, 21 November 1951
  - Dunlap, Leslie W, 9 November 1943
  - Dunlop, John, 15 February 1945
  - Dürr, 5 June 1936
  - Durr, Anthony, 24 February 1965
  - Dvoretzky, Edward, 21 May 1970
  - Dyck, Martin. (7), 21 January 1956 –26 April 1961
- E
  - Eberle, K, 25 October 1936
  - Eberle, Josef and Else, 30 December 1958
  - Eck, Harvey O, 14 November 1960
  - Eckert, J. S, 25 January 1940
  - Edelmann, M. (60), 23 January 1934 –13 June 1973
  - Edge, Hoyt, 26 July 1967
  - Edgeloe, V. A, 11 January 1961
  - Edwards, Francis Ltd. (11), 22 August 1951 –11 May 1972, undated
  - Edwards, H. W. (9), 3 December 1951 –16 April 1960
  - Eger, Tina, 17 January 1965
  - Eggers, H, 19 November 1971
  - Egner, Madeline, 23 August 1960
  - Ehlert, Arnold D, 24 January 1950
  - Eichner, Frederike, 1 June 1953
  - Eichner, Hans. (9), 20 April 1954 –23 May 1974, undated
  - Eisan, Marian, 8 March 1972
  - Eisenberger, Agnes, 9 November 1966
  - Eisenhower, M. S, 28 July 1942
  - Eissler, K. R. (3), 24 April 1952 -9 October 1952
  - Elder, Granville W, 4 November 1947
  - Elder, Lorene. L, 23 September 1942
  - Elkinton, Howard W. (2), 18 April 1953 -22 April 1953
  - Elton, William, 4 September 1959
  - Elwert, Wilhelm Braun, 10 July 1959
  - Emrich, Wilhelm. (2), 20 November 1971 –28 November 1971
  - Engasser, Quirin. (2), 2 May 1951 -8 April 1951
  - Endres, Jackie. (2) Undated
  - Engel, Irma, 29 December 1948
  - Engelbrechten, Margereta, 13 September 1931
  - Engelhardt, Elsa T, 3 December 1947
  - Engelhardt, H. T. (2) Undated
  - Engelsing, Rolf, 21 March 1973
  - Epstein, Bernard. Undated
  - Epstein, Fritz T, 18 October 1943
  - Epstein, Glenn, 28 May 1943
  - Epstein, Sam, 2 March 1943
  - Eruss, Fritz. Undated
  - Essel, Hermann, 7 June 1972
  - Esterly, Harry A, 10 August 1960
  - Evans, Anne, 26 March 1942
  - Evans, Griffith C, 9 October 1940
  - Everitt, E. B. (3), 13 October 1954 –1 November 1954, undated
  - Exner, Richard. (3), 22 April 1958 –22 November 1971
  - Eyster, William H, 15 October 1947
- F
  - von Faber du Faur, Curt. (31), 25 June 1940 –16 December 1958, undated (Box 2)
  - Fagerström, Grace, 20 May 1946 (Box 2)
  - Fairley, Barker. (44), 16 January 1948 –1959 (Box 2)
  - Falk, Robert, 1 December 1955 (Box 2)
  - Falk, W. E, 10 October 1946 (Box 2)
  - Faris, Ellsworth, 30 April 1936 (Box 2)
  - Faulkner, E. H, 31 October 1946 (Box 2)
  - Faust, Mrs. Albert B, 1954 (Box 2)
  - Faust, Theodora. Undated (Box 2)
  - Fehderau, Harold, 7 November 1953 (Box 2)
  - Feise, Ernst. (4), 25 August 1940 –21 August 1943 (Box 2)
  - Feldman, Theo and Anne. (51), 7 November 1947 –9 December 1958, undated (Box 2)
  - Felegy, Pauline, 7 February 1964 (Box 2)
  - Fenstermacher, Charlotte E. Undated (Box 2)
  - Ferdl, ? (3), 8 January 1958 –24 September 1965 (Box 2)
  - Ferguson, Edward. (2), 1 September 1970 –3 March 1972 (Box 2)
  - Ferguson, John. (2), 9 October 1960 –1 November 1960 (Box 2)
  - Ferry, W. H, 9 March 1961 (Box 2)
  - Fessen, Fred, 1944 (Box 2)
  - Fickert, Kurt J. (2), 9 May 1972 –17 May 1972 (Box 2)
  - Fields, Emmett B. (2), 16 June 1967 –9 June 1969 (Box 2)
  - Fife, Robert Herndon. (10), 2 June 1942 –22 September 1967, undated (Box 2)
  - Finckh, Alice H. (5), 26 February 1952 –13 December 1955 (Box 2)
  - Finsh, William C, 12 November 1967 (Box 2)
  - Fischer, Katherine. (12), 20 March 1943 –12 April 1949, undated (Box 2)
  - Fischer, Klaus P. (2), 23 March 1974 –4 April 1974 (Box 2)
  - Fisher, John Hurst, 11 January 1968 (Box 2)
  - Fisher & Fisher, 24 November 1942 (Box 2)
  - Fitton, Helen G, 9 March 1946 (Box 2)
  - Flajole, Edw. S, 18 June 1958 (Box 2)
  - Flanagan, Dennis. (2), 2 September 1949 -31 October 1949 (Box 2)
  - Flatt, Mrs, 11 June 1965 (Box 2)
  - Fleck, J. Undated (Box 2)
  - Fleischman, Henry B, 13 June 1974 (Box 2)
  - Fleischman, J. Michael, 27 June 1974 (Box 2)
  - Fleischman, Wolfgang Bernard. (37), 4 August 1959 –14 January 1967, undated (Box 2)
  - Fleming, Sam, 12 September 1963 (Box 2)
  - Fleming, Tommye, 4 June (Box 2)
  - Fletcher, H. M. (7), 8 November 1945 –6 May 1952 (Box 2)
  - Flöckel, Heinrich. (4), 10 October 1954 -11 December 1966 (Box 2)
  - Flygt, Sten, 22 November 1955 (Box 2)
  - Fogg, John M. Jr. (6), 28 July 1949 –16 November 1949 (Box 2)
  - Foley, Daniel J, 26 November 1952 (Box 2)
  - Fontenay, Charles L, 4 June 1966 (Box 2)
  - Forster, Leonard W. (2), 10 November 1969 -15 January 1971 (Box 2)
  - Forster-Wegnert, Hild, 2 June 1948 (Box 2)
  - Fotheringay, Reginald T, 11 July 1966 (Box 2)
  - Fowler, Julian S, 28 October 1943 (Box 2)
  - Fraley, Ann, 11 July 1960 (Box 2)
  - Francke Verlag Bern. (2), 17 March 1949 -29 July 1972 (Box 2)
  - Frank, Luanne. (2), 27 September 1972 –26 January 1973 (Box 2)
  - Frank, Margaret H, 15 February 1951 (Box 2)
  - Frankfurter, Felix, 1 July ? (Box 2)
  - Franz, Günther, 24 September 1970 (Box 2)
  - Fredebaugh, Marna, 18 June 1970 (Box 2)
  - Frederking, W. Undated (Box 2)
  - Freiburger Bücherstube. (3), 12 February 1931 –March 1936 (Box 2)
  - Freitas, Bill and Margarete. (6), 28 July 1964 –24 December 1969 (Box 2)
  - Frenz, Horst. (2), 4 February 1956 –8 December 1958 (Box 2)
  - Freuman?, George. Undated (Box 2)
  - Freund, Max, 31 October 1942 (Box 2)
  - Frey, John R. (12), 10 February 1953 –8 May 1971 (Box 2)
  - Friedel, Henry K, 14 August 1954 (Box 2)
  - Friedman, Arthur, 17 June 1970 (Box 2)
  - Friedrich, Werner. P, 8 April 1953 (Box 2)
  - Friesen, Gerhard. (28), 28 December 1967 -26 March 1974, undated (Box 2)
  - Fringeli, Dieter. (4), 27 July 1967 -16 May 1973, undated (Box 2)
  - Fritsch, Robert R. (3), 20 December 1949 –30 January 1950 (Box 2)
  - Fuchs, A. (19), 26 June 1948 –8 July 1955 (Box 2)